This is a full-on retreat! Everyone get to the airport!
The escape helicopter should be waiting for us.
All right, then, let's fall back.
Do whatever it takes to get there alive!
Move it!
Go!
Stop!
её!
I saw you
Racketcumulac!
He went.
Damn it.
You, hey, listen to me.
You're not safe out here in the open, and I can't keep carrying you.
You've got to open your eyes and get up.
You, come on!
Wake up!
I'm not healing.
At this rate, I'm going to.
Let's get up.
Ah!
Please, help me!
You guys, he's gonna kill me!
Run away!
No, stop!
Blood, I just need a little...
New monster!
Ugh...
Your devotion to those you care about is overwhelming.
When your family's in danger of being harmed, you lose all sense of right and wrong.
That's gonna get us in trouble one of these days, don't you think, you?
What am I doing here?
Please don't tell me I'm dead again.
Not this time. You've been knocked unconscious.
Wait, Gurren! What happened back there?
See, this is what I was talking about.
You're always obsessing over someone.
Yeah, whatever. Just tell me Gurren, Shinoa, and the others are fine.
I have no idea if they are.
I can only see what you see, and your eyes have been closed for a while now.
Then, they might still have Gurren.
Gurren? Yeah, sure.
But it's a different member of your family you should be worried about.
Where am I? Hello?
It can't be.
No way.
Mika, is that you?
Mika!
Stop! What are you doing?
Blood.
Come on!
I need to drink some blood!
It...
It hurts.
Hey, what's happening?
Mika can't fight it!
I need blood!
The thirst is too painful!
I can't take it!
I'm so sorry, Mika.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have left you all alone.
What did I almost do?
Sorry.
I wasn't myself just now.
Is it really that bad?
If you don't drink blood, I mean.
This is all because I left you behind.
No, like I told you before, I...
Mika!
No, stay back.
I don't want to hurt you, and I don't trust myself right now.
But you're hurt.
Don't worry about yourself, not me!
Besides, there are some things we need to talk about.
Whatever you have to say can wait, damn it!
I just got you back, and now you're gonna die?
You can't do that!
Please don't leave me, Mika!
Blood will heal you.
Take what you need.
Do it.
Please, you have to stay away from me.
I can't keep fighting.
It's too powerful.
Just do it.
If it's gonna save you, then drink all you want.
What's the matter?
Hey, come on.
We've been reunited.
Finally.
I'm not going to lose you again, Mika.
I can't.
I won't.
No, you don't understand.
There's no going back if I do that.
If I drink human blood, even a drop, I'll be a complete vampire.
One who will never age.
There won't be a shred of humanity left in me.
Okay, but that still means it'll save you.
We won't be separated again.
Hey, come on.
Can't you just do me this one tiny favor and stay alive?
I can't.
Wrong answer.
If you don't want to do it, I'll have to make you.
I said no, dammit!
I've been fighting it so long, with everything in my power.
I don't want to be a monster.
I don't want you to see me as some grotesque creature.
So I've swallowed down my thirst.
It wasn't easy.
And now you're telling me-
Of course it's not easy, dummy!
Do you really think I want to watch my best friend turn into a vampire?
But tell me, Mika, what other choice do I have?
If you die here, then I'll-
I'll-
I'll have to start crying!
You've gotta be kidding me.
I don't care if you become a monster.
You'll survive.
So just suck it up and do it for me!
You can't be serious.
You want me to become a vampire so you don't have to cry?
Yeah, I do.
You got a problem with that?
Yeah.
Jeez, you haven't changed a bit since we were kids.
I'm offering.
It's not like you're attacking me.
Besides, I don't know if I believe you really fought it all that hard
if you're willing to die even though survival is right in front of you.
If you wanted to die, then you should have done it in secret somewhere.
Listen, you.
I'm here because you need to know what the humans are-
La la la la la la!
I can't hear you, Mika!
Come on.
Please listen.
Okay, but only if you'll agree to drink my blood.
Stay alive for me.
I refuse to let you die.
Just go ahead and give in to your thirst.
You know, you're an awful person.
Maybe.
But you've only got yourself to blame for making me your family.
Biggest mistake of my life.
I'm gonna become a monster because of you.
I'm gonna keep living.
We'll still be family, no matter what you become.
I'm sorry.
It's so hard to resist.
I want to drink blood so badly.
Welcome back, Mika.
It's weird, right?
All of this.
Everything.
Drinking your family's blood just to stay alive.
It's not normal.
So what?
Like we care about being normal.
That's true.
Still, it's strange.
Never thought I'd become a real vampire.
You know, reminds me of something Gurren said.
Gurren?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot you don't know everyone.
He's the army guy who found me after I escaped from the vampires.
He took me in and cared for me.
He likes to talk, and he gives good advice.
He told me to keep on living, even if it was just for revenge.
That one day, someone who needed my help would show up and give me a new reason to exist.
That's why I'm still alive.
Even when life felt pointless.
Even when I thought no one needed me.
I forced myself to get through each day.
And I'm glad.
Because I finally got to see you again.
Hey, let's make a promise.
We'll survive together, even if it's painful sometimes.
Who cares if you're a vampire?
If it's too difficult for you, then I'll just have to turn you back into a human.
So please, promise me you won't give up and try to die ever again.
Oh, the irony.
I fought all this time because I thought you needed saving.
But you're the strong one.
Guess you have changed in some ways.
What?
Come on, I've always been the strong one.
No, you used to be a real big crybaby.
Huh?
You're the one who's bawling right now!
Okay, you got me there.
Well, if you really think I'm stronger than before, then it's probably all because of Gurren's training.
You may think that, but this Gurren guy you keep talking about is just using you...
I know he's got his own plans.
But he's part of my family, too.
I was as good as dead when my parents abandoned me.
I thought life was over.
But you and Gurren both made me want to keep living.
You guys are the only reason I'm here today.
So you see?
I can never pay either of you back for all that you've done.
So I don't mind if you use me.
I'm nothing like those human bastards, you.
I'd never manipulate you the way that they are.
You say that, but you did drink my blood.
Yeah.
I'm just messing with you.
I don't care about the blood.
But I do have a small favor to ask.
What is it?
My teammates.
My family is in trouble.
Please, come with me.
Okay?
No, wait.
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Think about this.
You can't go back to those humans.
Just hear me out first.
I'm begging you.
This isn't good.
How long have I been out for?
Please, you.
Mika.
You're the one who carried me out here.
That means you must have some idea of what happened to my teammates.
Would you stop worrying about those humans and start paying attention to me?
I don't know what kind of awful brainwashing they've put you through.
But I can't let you go back to the army.
They're evil.
They've been experimenting on you and me since we were just kids.
See ya.
Why won't you listen to me?
You can't stop me.
Fine.
What are you doing?
Did you really pull a sword on me?
I'll do whatever it takes to protect you.
If that's the case, then you should be helping me.
Helping you?
Kill me if you don't want me to go.
Because I'd rather die than fail to protect my family.
You're such a hypocrite.
You said I had to survive even if it meant becoming a vampire.
Mika.
I won't let you go back to them.
Just hear what I have to say.
Stop!
They're my family, just like you are.
I think I've met the people you're talking about.
You have?
Tell me everything.
Where did you see them?
Hey, answer me.
Earlier, there was a girl.
She and her friends saved my life.
She fought with a scythe.
That's them.
I told you they're good guys.
Right?
That means we should be helping them out.
Yeah?
Only your friends.
I'll help the four of them.
That's great.
Hey, what are you doing?
Cut it out.
All right, let's get out of here.
We've got work to do.
Where do you think they are?
I don't know for sure.
But I did hear them say something about meeting at an airport.
So, what's going on, Shinwa?
I don't know anything more than you do.
I thought there were supposed to be helicopters.
But this place is deserted.
There aren't even any cars around.
I could have driven, you know.
I'm good at it.
I thought you said you wanted us both to survive.
Oh, shut up.
So?
You wanted to talk?
Right.
The humans have ulterior motives.
They're using you as a test subject for experimentation.
Is that all?
I already knew that.
The experiment will have far-reaching consequences.
And as a result, humans and vampires across the globe are targeting you.
Humans and vampires?
Wow, I had no idea I was so popular.
This is serious.
It's the same experiment that messed up the world.
The reason all of the adults died years ago.
It almost made humans extinct.
Hold up a second.
Are you saying it's my fault the world was almost destroyed?
No, you.
We didn't do any of this.
We were innocent kids who were being used.
Humans are the ones who caused this.
The Hyakuya orphanage where we lived was nothing but a laboratory.
After it was gone, the Japanese Imperial Demon Army took over the experimentation.
The experiment's called Seraph of the End.
Humans are ugly creatures.
They're animals driven by greed.
They only want to make themselves stronger.
They'll hurt anyone to get more power.
I can't leave you in the hands of people like that.
Mika, I'm also a human.
And if it's at all possible, I want to turn you back into one too.
So it's not like you can say all of humanity is bad.
If the wrong people have you under their control, they could use you to end this world in a heartbeat.
Run away with me instead.
We'll make a new home somewhere secluded, far away from this warp.
Where no one can find us.
The vampires or the moon demon company.
That's right.
This reminds me of another time.
Remember how we ran away from the vampires because we thought we could find paradise somewhere else?
Yeah.
But it didn't work.
Everyone got killed and we learned that paradise didn't exist.
Instead, there's only one thing.
This world.
I don't think there's anywhere else left for us to go.
Isn't it worth looking, though?
If so, then we can discuss that with my friends.
They're smart.
They can help us run away if that's what you really want us to do.
And you're certain we can trust them, you?
Sure, don't worry.
They're the good guys.
Trust them just as much as you trust me.
Okay?
They're the good guys.
You
Next time on Seraph of the End, Arrogant Love.